By His Majesty's oral decree,
Shen Mo, Registrar of the Penal Department,
has shown merit in investigating cases
and is observant of the finest details.
He is hereby promoted to Vice Director of the Imperial Astronomical Bureau.
He shall take up the post immediately,
assist the Director,
and help observe anomalies in celestial phenomena.
Respect this.
Vice Director of the Imperial Astronomical Bureau.
I have shallow qualifications.
How can I be worthy?
It is His Majesty's divine will.
I dare not guess it.
The carriage is ready.
Please depart immediately, Vice Director Shen.
Your father
is right under the Black Tower of the Imperial Astronomical Bureau.
Lord Qin, are you not going?
I have other important matters.
My lord.
We have arrived at the Imperial Astronomical Bureau.
The ninth floor of the Black Tower of the Imperial Astronomical Bureau.
It is the central hub of the formations
and also the entrance to the Dragon Vein.
Vice Director Shen.
Please follow me.
Those veins are not still.
But faintly pulsating to a certain rhythm.
Like a living creature.
Vice Director Shen.
The Director ordered that
since you are exhausted from the journey,
you should rest first.
Someone will deliver three meals a day.
The formations inside the tower are complex.
Please do not wander around at night
to avoid triggering the restrictions.
Is my father, Shen Qingshan, inside the tower?
I do not know.
This room.
The ninth floor.
It's all blood.
Whose blood?
The Dragon Vein.
Drinks blood.
It drank a lot.
Blood crystal powder.
Mixed with cinnabar.
Someone is warning me.
Vice Director Shen.
The Director summons you.
Lead the way.
Vice Director Shen.
You've had a hard journey.
From today on,
you will stay by my side.
The truth about the Dragon Vein,
I
will tell you slowly.
The jade pendant is the same.
This person.
Who exactly is he?
Some matters of the past,
there is no need to rush.
During tomorrow's morning lesson,
I will explain the matters inside the tower to you.
Yes.
Lord Director.
Very good.
Go back to your room and rest first.